<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on BSidesROC</title>
    <link>https://www.bsidesroc.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on BSidesROC</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2017 Survey Results</title>
      <link>https://www.bsidesroc.com/blog/2017-survey-results/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bsidesroc.com/blog/2017-survey-results/</guid>
      <description>Below you will find some of the results from the 2017 Attendee Survey. We asked you what you felt about various subjects and almost half of the attendees responded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank You</title>
      <link>https://www.bsidesroc.com/blog/thank-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bsidesroc.com/blog/thank-you/</guid>
      <description>Thanks again to everyone that made BSidesROC happen: our sponsors, our organizers, our volunteers, our friends and our attendees. We will update our website with stats about the conference including survey results. Check back here soon and we&amp;rsquo;ll see you in 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Food Update</title>
      <link>https://www.bsidesroc.com/blog/food-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bsidesroc.com/blog/food-update/</guid>
      <description>Here is an update on plans for Breakfast and Lunch:
Breakfast: We will have coffee and water available for all attendees to start their morning. But no actual food will be served. RIT has restaurants that will be open if you get hungry in the morning.
Lunch: For lunch, we&amp;rsquo;ve contacted Whole-E Roasters and The Meatball Co. food trucks wich will pull up to the north entrance of the GCCIS building where BSIdesROC will be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>T-Shirt Tickets Available Until Wednesday 4/5</title>
      <link>https://www.bsidesroc.com/blog/t-shirt-tickets-available-until-wednesday-4/5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bsidesroc.com/blog/t-shirt-tickets-available-until-wednesday-4/5/</guid>
      <description>This coming Wednesday, April 5th at noon, the option to pre-purchase a T-shirt with your ticket will come to an end. This is the only way you can be sure that you&amp;rsquo;ll get your hands on this year&amp;rsquo;s design. Yes, we will be selling shirts day of the conference but we will have a small number of them and, as with every year, they will sell out. Grab your T-shirt ticket today!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rochester InfraGard Will Be There</title>
      <link>https://www.bsidesroc.com/blog/rochester-infragard-will-be-there/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bsidesroc.com/blog/rochester-infragard-will-be-there/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re pleased to announce the Rochester chapter of InfraGard will join us at BSidesROC 2017. They will have a table setup; stop by and meet alliance members!
Find out more about the Rochester chapter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sponsor Announcement - NCC Group</title>
      <link>https://www.bsidesroc.com/blog/sponsor-announcement---ncc-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bsidesroc.com/blog/sponsor-announcement---ncc-group/</guid>
      <description>NCC Group will sponsor BSidesROC again this year! NCC Group is a trusted security firm with an unrivaled suite of services. More than 2000 employees in 35 offices around the world provide their expert skills to over 15,000 clients. Did you know they have a Rochester presence? Talk to the organizers if you would like to get in touch.
NCC Group is hiring everywhere!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tickets on sale again</title>
      <link>https://www.bsidesroc.com/blog/tickets-on-sale-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bsidesroc.com/blog/tickets-on-sale-again/</guid>
      <description>Despite what you may have heard, tickets are for sale. You can still sign up for training and for entry into the con. Hint: Grab your ticket shirts this week!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Training Day Announcement!</title>
      <link>https://www.bsidesroc.com/blog/training-day-announcement/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bsidesroc.com/blog/training-day-announcement/</guid>
      <description>Come one come all to the BSidesROC Training Day. We&amp;rsquo;re finally announcing the classes that we&amp;rsquo;ll have available the day before the BSidesROC conference. Today, attendees can sign up for classes related to network penetration testing, malware analysis, WiFi hacking, and social engineering. We&amp;rsquo;ve worked with our trainers to keep the classes at a reasonably low price.
Visit our Training Day page for details and directions for buying a ticket.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sponsor Announcement - F5</title>
      <link>https://www.bsidesroc.com/blog/sponsor-announcement---f5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bsidesroc.com/blog/sponsor-announcement---f5/</guid>
      <description>This week we have confirmed that our new friends at F5 are supporting BSidesROC 2017 as a Gold Sponsor! Many thanks to them and their team. If you want to learn more about how interesting F5 is, you&amp;rsquo;ll have a chance to talk with them at their table this year.
Find out more information here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sponsor Announcement - GreyCastle Security</title>
      <link>https://www.bsidesroc.com/blog/sponsor-announcement---greycastle-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bsidesroc.com/blog/sponsor-announcement---greycastle-security/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re happy to announce that GreyCastle Security are sponsors of BSidesROC, again! GreyCastle Security is the leading cybersecurity services provider dedicated exclusively to cybersecurity and the practical management of cybersecurity risks. By the way, did you know they have a Rochester office?
Find out more about career opportunties here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sponsor Announcement - RIT Department of Computing Security (CSEC)</title>
      <link>https://www.bsidesroc.com/blog/sponsor-announcement---rit-department-of-computing-security-csec/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bsidesroc.com/blog/sponsor-announcement---rit-department-of-computing-security-csec/</guid>
      <description>If you’ve been to more than one BSidesROC before, you may have noticed the difference in venues over the years. Starting last year, BSidesROC has been lucky to partner with RIT’s CSEC department and have them host us on their campus in the GCCIS building. CSEC is on the front line of security and continues to be one of the top colleges in the nation for infosec.
Find out more information about their program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sponsor Announcement - Secure Network Technologies</title>
      <link>https://www.bsidesroc.com/blog/sponsor-announcement---secure-network-technologies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bsidesroc.com/blog/sponsor-announcement---secure-network-technologies/</guid>
      <description>Once again, we are pleased to announce that Secure Network Technologies has signed on to help make BSidesROC successful! If you’ve never heard of them, you’re missing out on an awesome company. They do everything from traditional pen testing to full scale red team physical security evaluations. They also go above &amp;amp; beyond to help the community, providing critical support to BSides events, donating high-quality gear to the local hacker space, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>